http://soniclear.com/privacy-policy

626.584.9706
SoniClear Privacy PolicyLast Updated Dec 4, 2018 SoniClear Customer Data UsageSoniClear gathers personal information from customers in the course of doing business. This includes, for example, customer names, phone numbers, and email addresses. This information is only used in connection with sales and support of SoniClear products and is never provided to third parties for any other purpose.  SoniClear Cloud ServicesSoniClear offers optional cloud services, such as voice-to-text transcription. SoniClear does not disclose the information to third parties, except as required to implement the offered service (such as the use of third party cloud service providers). A variety of industry standard methods are used to protect the information uploaded to the cloud server. Privacy information is provided when you sign up for a SoniClear Cloud service. Please consult the specific information for the services you are using for details. What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.  How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. To quickly process your transactions. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.  How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.  Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.  Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include our business. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please send an email to "unsubscribe@soniclear.com" indicating you wish to no longer receive emails. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production. Please also note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.  In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Third party links  Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on November 11, 2016.  Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.  Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Your consent Google TrackingSoniClear uses Google Analytics to provide information about how visitors use the website. Google tracks web page retrieval from the website, providing SoniClear with reports on website activity. The tracking information may also be used to coordinate the display of advertising in connection with SoniClear products. SoniClear does not have any knowledge or control over how the data collected by Google is used.If you do not wish to allow Google to gather this information, you can opt out of Google tracking using a tool that they provide. More information is available at this Google Support Page.  AdRoll TrackingSoniClear uses AdRoll to track usage of the SoniClear website and provide remarketing advertisements to customers who have visited the site.If you do not wish to allow AdRoll to gather this information, you can opt ot of AdRoll tracking using a tool that they provide. More information is available at this AdRoll Support Page.
